# SELENA RAMIREZ

A Master Certified Coach with 10+years of experience, specializing in life coaching, client relations, professional development, and career coaching. A proventrack record of aiding clients in overcoming life obstacles, financial burdens, and relationship issues.

123 Bedford Avenue. New York, NY, 12345 se len a ram irez@exa m pl exom (123) 456-7890

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### LIFE COACH

Personal Coaching Co., New York, NY May 2016-Present

- Provide life coaching and career coaching services to 150+ clients across various ages, backgrounds, and industries, including facilitatingone on one sessions to evaluate client issues and build strategies according to individual needs
- Achievea client satisfaction rating of 94% on customer surveys and lead training initiatives to improve Google ratings from 3.9 stars to 4.7 stars over two years
- Coordinate with a team of senior life coaches to create a webinar series providing insights into how to achieve and maintain a healthy work-life balance

# LIFE COACH

Selena Ramirez Coaching Firm, New York, NY May 2011-May 2016

- ◆ Delivered personal coaching sessions to 75+ unique clients with varying needs and experience levels, provided emotional support, and delivered education to clients on available resources for mental health needs
- Analyzed long-term career goals, professional experience, and qualifications and provided recommendations to support clients in achieving long-term success

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Psychology

Columbia University, New York, NY Sep tern be r 2007 - May 2011

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Learning and Development
- ♦ Life Coaching
- ♦ Career Coaching
- ♦ Leadership Development
- ♦ Engagement Strategy

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Ma ste r Ce rti fied Coa ch (M CC), International Coach Federation (ICF), 2017
- Professional Certified Coach (PCC), International Coach Federation (ICF), 2014
- Associate Certified Coach (ACC), International Coach Federation (ICF), 2011